Sniper Island Oh, the
wind carries my name.
From Sniper Island far away.
When I take aim, it's straight and true.
Blue, blue, la, la, blue.
Whether you're a man or a man, go on.
I will put your heart in my sights.
No one knows what secrets
hide behind this past edging.
Blue, blue, blue, the la, la, la.
There is no escape?
Snipers, sniper, sniper.
Sniper, he hates King, it's true.
The ring carries my name.
From Sniper Island far away.
What the hell is he doing over there?
Come on, just humor the poor guy.
He has too much pride to
show his face to the crew,
but he still wants to rescue his friend.
No one knows what secret I'd be.
Well, long as he stops singing, I guess.
Hey, get over here!
Oh, sure.
Okay, let's start the meeting
for Operation Rescue Robin.
We've never met before.
Don't you two have any questions about me?
So, the car you were
in was car number six.
That means that we've got five more left.
You know, like, where's Sniper Island?
But we don't know which
one of those Robin is in.
The answer is, it's in your heart.
And by the way, are you strong?
Are you kidding?
I'm super strong.
Even stronger than usual this week.
Remember, the point is to rescue
Robin, not beat the enemy.
At least in theory.
We're up against a lot of
Marines in a narrow space,
so we gotta make sure
we don't get surrounded.
We should avoid as many fights as we can
and whittle down the main force in turns.
Here we go. Listen up.
Okay, now I'm ready for battle.
Huh?
What's going on?
Don't you play innocent
with me, immoral girl!
Have you no shame changing your
clothes out here in front of everyone?
Shame is overrated.
What was I supposed to do?
The train only has one car.
Cover up your legs!
Cover up your stomach!
That goes for you two square-hand sisters!
People like you are corrupting society!
Whatever, you're just too shy. Shy boy.
Why you?
Stupid black shorts with
their stupid tiny pockets.
Come on!
Get in there!
Don't put meat in your pants, you idiot!
I'm starting to think you
might actually pull this off.
You certainly seem riled
up, if nothing else.
You bet we are!
Those jerks got away with Robin last time,
but now that I know what's going
on, they don't stand a chance!
I hope you're right, because if
you get stuck in something again,
you're going to have hell to pay you.
Nah don't worry I got a reason to
beat them this time around right?
Hey did you Change your weapon?
Nami oh no it's pretty much the same
one as before Usopp just improved it
with some dials after we got back from
Skypea this is The perfect climate act?
I see so that's his right?
It's Usopp's
Last work
Don't get all sad now!
You ready?
Let's do this.
An intruder?
Uh, yes, sir.
That's what I heard.
It's not feasible to board the
Puffing Tom while it's running.
If there really is an intruder,
that means we let him sneak
on board before we departed.
What an embarrassment.
I agree, sir.
It's inexcusable.
But if you can't get on while the train
is moving, you can't get off either.
That means the intruder, as well as the
missing prisoners, are still here somewhere.
You just have to find them. Yes, sir.
Captain T-Bone, I don't think there's
any room for someone to hide in here.
Good evening!
It's them!
They were right outside!
We found three suspicious men,
including the criminals in Car 7!
Corner and capture them!
Ever use a hammer before?
You sure do suck. Shut up!
There's no point in resisting.
Open the door already!
They're gonna break through! I know.
This way!
They found the intruder in car seven.
The criminals do?
Yeah, let the guys in car three know.
That Franky guy's in a lot of trouble.
Move in and capture them alive!
Move it! Stand back!
Whoa!
They're shooting at us!
Then hurry it up!
A little help would be nice!
Don't shoot blindly!
We don't want these guys dead!
You're right.
What do we do, Captain T-Bone?
Allow me to handle this.
I hate crooked men and crooked swordplay.
Here comes my right-angle flash!
Bonsoir!
They're gone!
The roof!
Go!
They're at the end of the train!
Now, hurry!
Oh, no!
Everyone get back to the
front cars right now.
This is a trap!
What are you talking about?
Quick retreat.
They tricked us. huh.
We can't go back anymore.
The door's blocked.
No way.
The cars are detached.
Whoa!
Damn it! That's cheating!
You'll pay for this!
I was too late.
Have a safe trip, gentlemen!
Say hello to the Sea Kings for me!
Fare thee well!
That's two cars down.
Should cut the small fries
down by about 50 or so.
But aren't Luffy and the others
coming on the same railway?
What happens when the
cars run into each other?
Eh, they'll come up with something.
You arrogant thugs!
I'm gonna tear this door
down in you with it!
Oh, going for a swim?
All right.
Five to go.
You bastard!
You're gonna suffer for that one!
What will poor Captain T-Bone do?
Hey, report this to CP9!
Great, more of these guys.
And Freight has for T!
Sniper King!
Gunpowder Stark!
Strong right!
Heavyweight shot, fire!
Agh!
They hit him!
That hurt.
Keep shooting!
Why isn't the gun working on him?
Whoa, that was crazy.
What the hell are you?
Huh?
Oh, guess I forgot to
tell you. I'm a cyborg.
Those are real? Yep.
I got steel and weapons
built right into my body.
Still kind of hurts if I get shot,
and I might bleed a little too.
But no big deal.
Just when you think you've seen
it all, the world's a crazy place.
Awesome!
Oh...
What in the hell was that for? Huh?
You can deflect bullets, but needles hurt?
For one, I'm not your science
experiment, so stop poking me!
And for two, just so you know, my back
isn't the same as my front, get it?
I had to do the operation on myself,
so I couldn't reach around behind me.
In other words, only the
front side is cyborg.
While I'm at it, let me tell
you another little secret.
My belly's always cold.
Can you guess why?
How would I know?
It's because I got my own personal
fridge in there to keep my cola cold.
Wow, that's handy.
Man, that's got to be great in the summer.
Okay, the cola thing is really neat,
but we don't have time for this.
We've got to get moving to the next car.
This one is number four.
I'm Wanze!
Here I come!
What's up, you guys? Are you hungry?
You look hungry.
How about some ramen?
I'm the head steward of this train,
so I can cook anything you
fellas would like to eat.
Okay, ramen it is, but before I
start, a little trivia for you.
My nose hairs are shaped like this.
They crisscross inside, so they
look just like fishnet stockings.
This is very important.
First, I grab the flour.
Ant feet in...
No, no, take this!
Done!
Here... Oh, no!
Okay, that was a waste of time.
Listen, we've got someone
waiting on us, Wanze.
You'll have to enjoy that
nose ramen on your own.
Not so fast!
You'll have to defeat me first!
You think you can stop us?
I know I can!
This is an important escort mission,
so they've got an important guy
like me to keep the train safe!
If you want to rescue
that friend of yours,
then first you'll have
to defeat my Ramen Kenpo!
Ramen Kenpo?
I mean, keep gambling!
That little turd is making fun of me!
I know he's annoying, but
you gotta keep your cool!
How'd you like my idiot imitation?
Was it dumb enough for you?
Don't let him get to you.
Go, go, go, go, go!
This dude got ants in his pants or what?
I swear that I crazed him
with one of those shots.
But he doesn't even care.
He even looks happy.
I thought my heart was going
to leap out of my chest.
How was I supposed to know?
You made that same stupid
face for everything.
I'll take this guy down.
Just watch. Hold on.
You can't let this clown
get under your skin.
We got more important things to
do than sit here and play games.
You stay back and I'll
make quick work of him.
I don't know what your deal is?
But if you were a real chef, you'd conduct
yourself with a little more dignity.
I'm talking to you, stupid!
Why don't you take your
own advice for once?
But look!
He dodged that kick without even blinking!
In fact, he even looks happy!
I thought he was gonna die!
Stop making that damn face!
Don't do the same joke twice!
I've had enough.
Like I said, this guy is mine.
You go ahead.
I'll catch up with you two later.
So you're saying the rear
two cars were detached?
How could you allow something
like this to happen?
My deepest apologies, ma 'am.
But in our defense, even Captain T-Bone
got trapped in one of those cars,
and you know how powerful he is.
Fine.
Give me a status report on
what's left of the train.
Yes, ma 'am.
As of now, in addition to the engine
room, there are five cars still with us.
All of the military in the
fifth car have been taken out.
That leaves Wanze guarding the fourth car?
Nero on duty in the third car!
Nico Robin up in the first car?
and everyone here in the second car.
It seems our enemy is
not to be taken lightly.
However, the only
problem that concerns me?
In our current situation.
is that Franky is walking
around this train free.
Our mission was to take
Franky and Nico Robin into
custody and then deliver
them securely to Eni's lobby.
As long as we accomplish that,
I don't care how many men we lose
or how we take care of our enemies.
That has no bearing on our mission.
And were you able to
identify the intruders? Yes.
First there were the two
men that we had in custody,
but now it seems one of those two is
wearing some sort of strange mask.
There's also a blonde guy in a
suit that we've never seen before,
making a total of three intruders.
He's probably a member of the Straw Hat
Pirates just like that long-nosed man is.
Naturally, their purpose
here is to rescue Nico Robin.
And, since they freed him,
Frankie's decided to help them out.
Hey, Looch, would you like me to
go and keep an eye on Nico Robin?
That's not necessary.
Just stay focused on recapturing Franky.
Nothing else matters to him.
So, they want to take
Nico Robin back, do they?
Sorry to break it to them.
But that's just not gonna happen.
I won't let you pass!
Letting the heck out of the floor!
Is he gonna bring out
the ramen noodles again?
Ramen beans!
This is sharp!
Damn it!
Let's head over on the roof.
Right.
We'll leave it to you then, Sanji.
Best of luck.
Go, go, go, go!
They're go, go, go gone!
But I suppose that's no big deal.
Because the person waiting
for them in the next car?
is one tough customer, Nero!
He's the latest addition to
CP9, an assassin for justice.
Those two are dead meat.
If there's one thing that
Nero loves to do, it's kill.
Go, go, go, go!
Ah, flinchy.
Shoot!
I told you, I'm in a hurry here.
Okay then, fine.
Ramen Kenpo Noodle Slicer!
Let's see how you like this!
Fire escape lane!
Not only did you disrespect my beautiful
attack, you kicked me ten times,
didn't you?
Actually, it was twelve times.
Hey, you!
Are you secretly super
strong or something?
It's not really a secret.
Maybe you're just super weak.
Super weak!
Not even my old man would say
something like that to me!
How dare you!
I'm Woods!
I wouldn't let you get away with this!
Rude!
Besides, I was simply distracted
by your swirling eyebrows.
They make me dizzy.
That's why I fell for your attack.
Still, you're a good fighter.
Too bad you look weird.
Hey, you freak!
You're in no position to
call anyone weird looking!
After that failed attack,
I feel like I need to prove myself, so
I'm gonna show you something amazing!
This is why I was chosen
to escort those criminals!
Ramen Kimpo, secret technique!
Uh, what the hell is all that?
It's my incredible edible combat uniform!
Ramen's polo suit!
Now fight!
Go, go, go, go!
The secret of this
ramen kenpo technique is
controlling the three
moving noodles at will!
See?
Bastard, how dare you disgrace
food like that, you weirdo!
My speed, my power, and
my special abilities!
I'm at a different level now
in all those areas! Yeah!
If showing you isn't enough,
I'm gonna boot it into you! Go!
Just shut up already and get on with it.
But prepare yourself, cause I'm gonna make
you eat every last one of those noodles.
Question.
Who are you?
What are you doing up here?
The officer in charge of the third car,
a four powers master,
and a new recruit in CP9,
the sea weasel, Nero.
Unfortunately, I'm under
specific orders not to kill you.
You know, you being one of our
most important criminals and all.
All right, that's one half.
Now tell me what you're doing up
here on the roof of this train.
If you'd just waited inside,
I would have come to you.
Well, how was I supposed to know that?
You may have tried to cheat
and skip right past this car.
My, my, my.
That's rather cautious of you.
But in your line of work, you always
got to keep your guard up, right?
By the way, what's that
weird-looking thing there behind you?
Huh?
That was a dirty trick.
Of course it was!
They don't call me the King of Water
Seven's underworld for nothing.
Don't go down, Octoshoes.
Who knows, is that you?
Why are you here?